don't you hate when this happens don't
you hate when you're at home just
sitting there you join yourself in your
restroom right halfway through you look
to the left though there's no toilet
paper right so then you get down and you
squat over to the sink that's sounded
like 12 you laugh and what do the rest
of you do the rest you just get up like
oh well and you go on no don't lie to me
I'm not lying to you we all do the same
thing you just squat over to the sink
right you look underneath there there's
none there so you go over to the kitchen
right to look for paper towels and
napkins there's none there so you go
over to Walgreens isn't that the worst
it's embarrassing
she's gotta have fun in life that's what
I'm about right life is beautiful in it
okay two people I'm enjoying it man you
know I'm enjoying live I just turned 37
right yeah still young but there's signs
yeah it's happening like I got my first
great nose hair
that one's stubborn it's deep in there
it's sick I didn't know what to do with
it I color with a sharpie I'm a little
dizzy right now I tried to get it before
the show with my man tweezers every man
knows what I'm talking around right you
ever reach deep in your nose for that
route hoping that okay he's done it
obviously right it's okay man it's a
manly thing to do all right you get back
there and you just cut here you don't
have said but it's one tear like a man
has one full of testosterone you know
your ancestor like he did us proud
you're lucky you pull out more you ever
just pull out four do you ever show it
to her look babe look at this get that
away from me that's disgusting
I think you that's light enough you're
good
oh man I'm enjoying life though man
right it's all about living life easy
isn't it you know you know I like to do
I'll tell you guys is I'm the type of
person that if I know I'm not gonna see
any tomorrow I'm gonna wear the same
clothes tomorrow anybody else like that
Yeah right cuz sometimes no you know
what Holly wore this for four hours and
it was mostly in air conditioning nobody
really saw it you know I kept my arms up
half of the time right
like I got a little pile of clothes in
the corner of my room that I call my
where again clothes anyone else got that
pile yeah outfits ready to go to actual
dirty socks in the basket on one of
those three times was it done right this
pile going strong quick sniff pants with
change in them shirts here it's already
under the sleeve Brent you know I'm
talking about its 48-hour protection I
still got a full day just rub it like
that that's all you got to do and the
crazy thing is that people think it's
lazy to wear the same clothes it's
actually tougher isn't it because you
got a void everywhere that you went the
day before like you just can't go to
your favorite places and if you see
somebody from the day before you have to
have an excuse you gotta be like hey
what's up how you do it just got out of
jail - my go-to excuse just me our eyes
you got do little things like that to
get out of stress right here's a few
tips right if you ever having a bad day
this is what I've learned all you got to
do is make somebody else's day worse
that's it that's it I'm not talking
about big things right like you've ever
had a bad day do this go to a public
restroom while someone's on the toilet
and just scream fire it's a bit better
and it's harmless
are you serious they're just on the
toilet just like no you laugh for 20
seconds you turn off the lights you walk
out it's the funniest thing ever some of
you are with me huh alright some of your
evil like me good cuz you understand we
love see people suck in situations don't
we does that make you feel a little good
like one of the best feelings in the
world is when you're driving on the
highway and there's no traffic in front
of you everything's clear but the other
side of the highway full of traffic
isn't that the best feeling ever
you feel like royalty like you feel good
you can speed up just to top them look
at this guy's speed up and slow down
again this laning in their lane and you
know what's better than that feeling
when you get to the end of their traffic
and you see all these cars zooming in
like crazy and you're just like you have
no idea oh my god once you get over that
hill it's gonna be terrible we love
seeing people suck in situations right
like everyone's done this everyone's
gone shopping right you finished your
grab your bag to start walking your car
in the parking lot
and as you're walking your car in the
parking lot a car starts to follow you
to figure out where your parts have you
at that moment yeah when they're right
behind you you can hear em dude
and what do we all do walk slower don't
we yeah every single person in here
takes their time no you're not rushing
me uh I'm a practice dance move right
now we all walk slower no one hears like
hold on wait beep beep here's my car
I'll get out you get in we all do the
same thing you walk really slow until
you halfway down the parking lot then
you zigzag through a car sorry my car
three rows down that's what you get for
following me someone did it to me I'm
doing it to you
oh hey comedy kids did you know that
Drybar comedy has their own app that's
right you could download it now and
watch my entire special and also special
to the other comedians that have
performed for Drybar comedy so go there
go check it out and laugh yourself silly